hopsti.com 2014-03-10

# 隐私权政策

Online Dating at Hopsti

Hopsti Privacy Policy

We do not send spam to or sell e-mail addresses.

Hopsti is an online social networking service. Members of its networking community set up personal profiles that can be inter-connected through networks of friends. Members can view other members' profiles; communicate with each other over the network, and share media files, comments, tags and web links to describe their interests. In this process, Hopsti request and display some personal information of members to other members and visitors, which allows our users to identify each other and expand their network of friends. Hopsti members can change their profile information at any time. By visiting our web site or its affiliated partners, you are accepting the terms and conditions of the privacy policy of Hopsti.

1\. Information Collected and Used by Hopsti

Hopsti collects member submitted account information such as name, email address, and birthday to identify members and to send notifications to those members relating to the Hopsti service. Hopsti also collects other profile data including but not limited to: personal interests, gender, age, education and occupation in order to assist members in finding and communicating with each other.

Hopsti also logs non-personally-identifiable information including IP address, profile information, aggregate user data, and browser type, from members and visitors to the site This data is used to manage the website, track usage and improve the website services. This non-personally-identifiable information may be shared with third-parties to provide more relevant services and advertisements to members. User IP addresses are recorded for security and monitoring purposes.

User Profile information including members' pictures and first names are displayed to people in order to facilitate user interaction in the Hopsti social networking community. Email addresses are used to invite new friends to join Hopsti, to add users to members' friends' networks, and to send notifications related to the service. With the exception of inviting friends, adding friends, and notifications, a user's email address is not shared or displayed to people within a user's personal network. Users within a personal network communicate on Hopsti with each other through the Hopsti service, without disclosing their email addresses. Users' full names are never directly revealed to other members.

From time to time, Hopsti or a partner may sponsor a promotion, sweepstake or contest on our website. Users may be asked to provide personal information including name, email address or home address or to answer questions in order to participate.

2\. Invitations and Other Communications to Non-members

Hopsti members can invite friends to join the network by sending invitation emails via our automated invitation system. Hopsti stores the email addresses that members provide so that the respondents may be added to the friend's list of the member sending the invitations. Hopsti does not sell these email addresses or use them to send any other communication besides invitations. Recipients of invitations from Hopsti may contact us to request the removal of their information from our database.

3\. Use of Cookies

Hopsti uses cookies to store visitors' preferences and to record session information. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. You may be able to configure your browser to accept or reject all or some cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set -- each browser is different, so check the "Help menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences -- however, you must enable cookies from Hopsti in order to use most functions on the site. Please note that we allow 3rd party advertisers that are presenting advertisements on some of our pages to set and access their cookies on your computer. Please also be aware that advertisers' use of cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not the Hopsti Privacy Policy.

4\. Links

Hopsti contains links to other websites, either provided by us or posted by members and visitors of the Hopsti website. Hopsti is not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices on other sites. When linking to another site a user should read the privacy policy stated on that site. Our privacy policy only governs information collected on Hopsti website.

5\. Publicly Published Contents

Please be aware that whenever you voluntarily post public information to the website that that information can be accessed by the public and can in turn be used by those people to send you unsolicited communications.

6\. Third Party Advertising

Ads appearing on this website may be delivered to users by Hopsti or one of our web advertising partners. Our web advertising partners may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement. In this way, ad servers may compile information about where you, or others who are using your computer, saw their advertisements and determine which ads are clicked on. This information allows an ad network to deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by Hopsti and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

7\. Correcting, Updating or Removing Information

Hopsti users may modify or remove any of their personal information at any time.

8\. Security

Hopsti's members' accounts are protected by member-created passwords. We take precautions to insure that member account information is kept private. We use reasonable measures to protect member information stored within our database, and we limit access to member information to those employees who need access to perform their job functions, such as customer service personnel and technical staff. Please note that we cannot guarantee the security of member account information. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors may compromise the security of member information at any time. If you have any further question about the security at our website, please contact us.

9\. Disclosure of Information

Hopsti Collects Except as described above, Hopsti will not disclose personal information to any third party without a member's explicit permission unless required by law. Hopsti reserves the right to transfer personal information to a successor in interest that acquires rights to that information as a result of the sale of Hopsti or substantially all of its assets to that successor in interest. For more information see the "Changes in Our Privacy Policy" section below.

10\. Changes in Our Privacy Policy

From time to time we may make changes to our privacy policy. If we make changes, we will post them on our site to make users aware of what the changes are so users will always be aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and when we may disclose it. A User is bound by any minor changes to the policy when she or he uses the site after those changes have been posted. If, however, we are going to use users' personally identifiable information in a manner materially different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify by posting a notice on our website.
